emulator-zone.com 2016-11-30

# The Emulator Zone - Privacy Statement

### Privacy Statement

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website ([The Emulator Zone](http://www.emulator-zone.com/)). 

#### Ads

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

#### Cookies

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive from our ad networks while visiting our site. 

For certain pages we also use a custom ad rotator which uses cookies to determine which ads you have seen already, so it may be able to avoid showing ads you've already seen. Information from this cookie is not used or stored for other purposes. 

#### Votes

If you vote for an emulator on this site, your IP address will be recorded in order to prevent you from voting twice for the same emulator. If you don't use the voting system to vote for an emulator your IP address will not be recorded by the voting system. 

#### Links

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those websites. 

#### Log files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, track user's movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

#### Contact us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or any other questions concerning the practices of this site, feel free to contact us at: [privacy@emulator-zone.com](mailto:privacy@emulator-zone.com)
